{
    "subject": "resource/Arizona_Christian_University",
    "predicate": "ontology/facultySize",
    "object": "80",
    "human_readable": "The faculty size of Arizona Christian University is 80.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9273837804794312,
            "question": "What is the approximate size of the faculty at Arizona Christian University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.881597101688385,
            "question": "Is the faculty size of Arizona Christian University relatively small or large?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8099653124809265,
            "question": "What is the average class size at Arizona Christian University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7439584732055664,
            "question": "How does the faculty size of Arizona Christian University compare to other universities?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7342054843902588,
            "question": "How many faculty members are there at Arizona Christian University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7028587460517883,
            "question": "Could you provide more information about the faculty at Arizona Christian University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6131048798561096,
            "question": "What are the qualifications and experience of the faculty at Arizona Christian University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48257628083229065,
            "question": "How does the faculty-to-student ratio at Arizona Christian University compare to other institutions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35699838399887085,
            "question": "Are there any trends in faculty size at universities in recent years?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3363777697086334,
            "question": "What other factors might influence the size of a university's faculty?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The faculty size of Arizona Christian University is 80.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7334_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any trends in faculty size at universities in recent years?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7334_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the faculty-to-student ratio at Arizona Christian University compare to other institutions?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7334_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the qualifications and experience of the faculty at Arizona Christian University?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7334_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7334_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7334_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7334_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7334_130.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7334_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7334_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7334_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7334_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7334_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7334_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response to your query:\n\n`{'output': 'no'}`\n\nExplanation: According to the provided context information, it is stated that \"This institution has a range of 50-99 academic employees (Faculty)\". Therefore, the faculty size of Arizona Christian University is not 80, but rather between 50 and 99."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe document states that the academic staff range at Arizona Christian University is between 50-99 employees, not 80. Therefore, the statement that the faculty size of Arizona Christian University is 80 is incorrect according to the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}